freebooksummary.com 2001-04-01

# Privacy Statement for health2us.com

## Privacy Statement for health2us.com

PII has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: health2us.com.

Your IP address is only used to help identify you and/or your shopping cart.

This site contains links to many other sites, but will not transfer your data to them.

**health2us.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders to our customers. The customer's contact information is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All credit card or electronic check processing and data storeage is done off site by secure processors. 

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send an email request to: [database@health2us.com](mailto:database@health2us.com)

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [database@health2us.com](mailto:database@health2us.com)

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

Fred Peschel PII 3516 Delilah Drive Cape Coral, FL. 33993 fred@health2us.com See details on our Colloidal Silver Generator for some amazingly simple health benefits! 

* * *

CHECK DAILY FOR ADDITIONS/CHANGES!   
Site Map | Order Form | Faith Healing | Chelation Therapy | Heart | Water/CS Testing | Enzymes | Cancer | Breast Cancer   
True Stories | Poison Ivy | Privacy statement | About PII | Colloidal Silver | Applications of Cs | Backpain | Acne | [ Subscribe Newsletter](mailto:subscribe@health2us.com?Subject=ADD%20me%20to%20newsletter)

BACK ONE PAGE  PRICE LIST   
For More info call 941-283-8640 or FAX 941-283-8631 or [EMAIL TO PII](mailto:pii@cyberstreet.com)   
or SNAIL MAIL TO: PII, 3516 DELILAH DRIVE, CAPE CORAL, FLORIDA 33993
